http://www.statamatrix.com/privacy-and-legal

Loading ...
Medical Device CE Certification
EU MDR (2017/745)
EU MDR Gap Assessment
EU Clinical Evaluation Reports (CER)
FDA IDE Submissions
Emergency Use Authorizations (EUA)
Blog
Public Training Course Dates & Information:
Download Catalog »
Private Training & Consulting Available
Request Info
Privacy and Legal
Updated February 13, 2020
Oriel STAT A MATRIX is committed to protecting the privacy of those using our website and the confidentiality of the personal information that visitors and customers share with us. We take appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect your personal information.
What personal information do we collect from you?
Personal information refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you, and information concerning your use of our website and activities at our website that may be connected to you.
Personal information is collected from you when you create an Oriel STAT A MATRIX account and / or register for a class, create or modify your online account, complete a “contact us” or “request more information” form, download content, make a purchase, or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect directly from you include your name, username, email address, postal address, phone number, employer’s name, transactional information (including services purchased or subscribed to and billing address), as well as any contact or other information you choose to provide.
In some cases, another user (such as an administrator) may create an account on your behalf and may provide your information, including your personal information in order to register or record your participation in a seminar. If you are an employee of one of our customers and would no longer like us to process your information, please contact your employer and us at the contact information provided below.
When you visit orielstat.com, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This information may include, but is not limited to, your internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, the web page you were visiting before you came to our site, and information you search for on our site.
Cookies – small data files stored by your browser on your device's hard drive for record-keeping purpose – are used to collect this information. Cookies used include "session ID cookies" in order to support login and main service functionality, as well as cookies of third-party providers like Google Analytics that allow us to collect user experience data (e.g., pages visited, time spent on the website), which we use to improve your overall experience on our site. Information collected by third parties is aggregated across multiple users and is not used to identify who the visitor was, or what is his/her Oriel STAT A MATRIX account (if any). You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the site or all functionality of our services.
Information related to seminars you attend is stored in orielstat.com, along with evidence of attendance and test results. Public seminar attendees are able to access this information by logging onto their Orielstat.com account.
How do we use your personal information?
We use information provided to orielstat.com to provide you with the information you requested; confirm and manage communications related to an order; respond to your comments, questions, and requests; and provide customer service and support.
We also use the information we collect about you to send you information related to your purchases, marketing information (including featured seminars and newsletters), and other news or information about Oriel STAT A MATRIX. You may opt out of receiving information that does not relate to a specific purchase or registration by visiting your profile and opting out of some or all correspondence.
Only with your prior consent, information pertaining to a training you participated in may be shared with the organization that certified the class (e.g., IRCA, Exemplar Global).
Information about our users may be employed to investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access to Oriel STAT A MATRIX services, and other illegal activities.
We also use personal information to understand user behavior and overall experience on our website.
How do we protect your data?
Oriel STAT A MATRIX does not sell, trade, or rent the personal information we collect. We will share your data only in the specific scenarios listed below.
For purchases paid for by credit card on our online store, your information is used to get approval from your credit card company.
For participants in training certified by third parties, we may request to share your information with the certifying body in order to satisfy requirements for attaining certification status for a particular class.
We may disclose your information to a third party if (a) we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; (b) to enforce our agreements, policies, and terms of service; (c) to protect the security or integrity of Oriel STAT A MATRIX services; (d) to protect Oriel STAT A MATRIX, our customers, or the public from harm or illegal activities; or (e) to respond to an emergency that we believe in good faith requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person. We may also share aggregated or anonymized information that does not directly identify you with third parties.
We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
How do I manage how much information I share or if I share any at all?
Visitors to orielstat.com residing within the EU are opted out of marketing communications by default
You can opt out of all marketing-related communications at any time. Every marketing-related communication includes an “unsubscribe” button to facilitate removal or preference updates. Please note, however, that you cannot opt out of communications related to registrations in our public seminars (e.g., course confirmations, invoices, course prework emails).
To update your Orielstat.com account information, log onto your account via orielstat.com and make any necessary changes; this will update your information pertaining to any public seminar registrations. You may also contact us directly at:
By email: privacy@orielstat.com
By post:
Oriel STAT A MATRIX
1095 Morris Avenue
Suite 103B
Union, NJ 07083
Attn: Privacy Control
By phone: 800.472.6477
Contact privacy@orielstat.com to request deletion or a copy of the data we’ve collected about you.
What is Oriel STAT A MATRIX doing to protect my privacy?
This site has security measures in place to protect it from the loss, misuse, and alteration of information under our control. Our servers use encrypted methods for the pages that contain personally identifiable data, including your credit card information and your address. We routinely monitor and upgrade our security systems to ensure that we use the best security technology available. Our hosting platform, Pier 1, complies with GDPR requirements.
Credit card transactions
Oriel STAT A MATRIX does not store your credit card information in our systems. All credit card transactions are processed using secure encryption – the same level of encryption used by leading banks. Card information is transmitted, stored, and processed securely at gateways on a PCI-compliant network.
In the case of a suspicious or declined transaction, our company may contact you to confirm the validity of the card and ensure your identity, or to cancel that transaction with full notification.
In the event that an order cannot be completed, please contact our Customer Service department (customerservice@orielstat.com). If our website cannot establish a secure connection, we will not risk your confidential information (i.e., the information will not be transmitted).
Conditions of use, notices, and revisions
If you choose to visit Orielstat.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this notice and our conditions of use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of New Jersey. If you have any concern about privacy at Orielstat.com, please send a thorough description to our Customer Service team (customerservice@orielstat.com) and we will try to resolve it.
Our business changes constantly. This notice and the conditions of use will also change, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the privacy notice in effect at the time of use. Please check our website frequently to see recent changes.
At Oriel STAT A MATRIX, we are sincerely committed to a safe and secure web experience for our visitors. If, after reading this, you have concerns or questions, please do not hesitate to contact us in one of the following ways:
Send an email to customerservice@orielstat.com
Send hard-copy mail to the following address:
Oriel STAT A MATRIX
1095 Morris Avenue
Suite 103B
Union, NJ 07083
Attn: Privacy Control
Cookie policy and usage
Oriel STAT A MATRIX automatically collects usage data through the use of cookies – small text files a website uses to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user’s ongoing access to the site, and facilitate the use of the site.
Different cookies do different things. Some are essential to the operation of a website, whereas others are not.
The information below describes the cookies we use on our site and why we use them. If you are located in the European Union, by clicking “Accept” you explicitly agreed to cookies being used while browsing the site. For detailed guidance explaining what cookies are and how to control or delete them, we recommend you visit http://www.youronlinechoices.eu.
The cookies we set
If you create an account with us, then we will use cookies for management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out; however, in some cases they may remain afterward to remember your site preferences when you’ve logged out. We use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are typically removed or cleared when you log out to ensure that you can only access restricted features and areas when logged in.
When you submit data to us through a form such as those found on contact pages or comment forms, cookies may be set to remember your user details for future correspondence. These are cookies that are set by this website directly and cannot be deactivated because they are required for the site to function. The web server uses nonpersistent cookies (not permanently saved on your computer) to save your choices while browsing the site. These are necessary cookies to support the basic functionality of the web experience (e.g., choice of language).
Google Analytics cookies
We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behavior. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here, and what you click on. This data is not tied to personally identifiable information. We do not collect or store your personal information (e.g., your name or address), so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.
This site uses Google Analytics, which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solutions on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit, so we can continue to produce engaging content.
As we sell products, it’s important for us to understand statistics about how many of the visitors to our site actually make a purchase, As such, this is the kind of data that these cookies will track. This is important to you, because it means that we can accurately make business predictions that allow us to monitor our advertising and product costs to ensure the best possible price.
You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy with regard to its analytics service at https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en.
Marketo cookies
This site uses an automation system provided by Marketo Inc., which employs cookies to recognize you as a unique user when you return to the site, and to track various data related to your website usage in order to provide custom content or services related to your specific interests.
The cookies placed by the Marketo server are readable only by Marketo. For more information on Marketo cookies and what they are used for, see the official Marketo site at http://www.marketo.com/trust/legal/privacy/.
Social media cookies
On our blog, you will see “social buttons.” These enable users to share or bookmark webpages or access Oriel STAT A MATRIX content on these social media sites. These buttons include Google+, Facebook “Like,” and LinkedIn “Share.” By clicking on any of these buttons, the site will register your action and may use that information.
To implement these buttons and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, scripts from domains outside of Oriel STAT A MATRIX must be used. You should be aware that when you are logged into the services of these sites (e.g., Google and Facebook), it is likely that they’re collecting information about your browsing habits, including when you’re on the Oriel STAT A MATRIX site, even if you do not click on a social button. Read the respective policies of each of these sites to see how they use your information and how to opt-out or delete such information.
Updates
We reserve the right change this cookie policy at any time. Any changes will become effective as soon as they are posted. Your continued use of our site constitutes your agreement to all such changes.
Disabling cookies
Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of this site. Therefore, it is recommended that you do not disable cookies. If you disagree with the use of cookies, you have the following options:
You can delete cookies after having visited the site.
You can browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” in Internet Explorer, and “Private Browsing” in Firefox and Safari).
You can set your browser’s security controls so that all or certain cookies are blocked.
You can request that we delete any personal information that we store – to do so, email privacy@orielstat.com.
Do not track
If you prefer not to use any cookies, you can also opt out in some browsers by turning on “Do Not Track” or visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices to opt out directly. We currently do not support Do Not Track browser settings, but are committed to supporting it in the future once there is a consistent industry standard for compliance.
How to contact us
If you have questions about this cookie policy, please contact us at: privacy@orielstat.com.
Request More Info
Share This Page
Subscribe to Newsletter
Request a Proposal
Or ask a question!
Get answers right now. Call 1.800.472.6477
1095 Morris Avenue
Suite 103B
Union, NJ 07083
Phone: 1.800.472.6477
Fax: 732.548.4085
International Offices
Online
Privacy and Legal
We use cookies to help us offer you the best online experience. By continuing to use our website or closing this window, you’re providing consent regarding cookies. If you want to learn more read our
Privacy Policy.
OK
×
Privacy and Legal
Updated February 13, 2020
Oriel STAT A MATRIX is committed to protecting the privacy of those using our website and the confidentiality of the personal information that visitors and customers share with us. We take appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect your personal information.
What personal information do we collect from you?
Personal information refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you, and information concerning your use of our website and activities at our website that may be connected to you.
Personal information is collected from you when you create an Oriel STAT A MATRIX account and / or register for a class, create or modify your online account, complete a “contact us” or “request more information” form, download content, make a purchase, or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect directly from you include your name, username, email address, postal address, phone number, employer’s name, transactional information (including services purchased or subscribed to and billing address), as well as any contact or other information you choose to provide.
In some cases, another user (such as an administrator) may create an account on your behalf and may provide your information, including your personal information in order to register or record your participation in a seminar. If you are an employee of one of our customers and would no longer like us to process your information, please contact your employer and us at the contact information provided below.
When you visit orielstat.com, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This information may include, but is not limited to, your internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, the web page you were visiting before you came to our site, and information you search for on our site.
Cookies – small data files stored by your browser on your device's hard drive for record-keeping purpose – are used to collect this information. Cookies used include "session ID cookies" in order to support login and main service functionality, as well as cookies of third-party providers like Google Analytics that allow us to collect user experience data (e.g., pages visited, time spent on the website), which we use to improve your overall experience on our site. Information collected by third parties is aggregated across multiple users and is not used to identify who the visitor was, or what is his/her Oriel STAT A MATRIX account (if any). You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the site or all functionality of our services.
Information related to seminars you attend is stored in orielstat.com, along with evidence of attendance and test results. Public seminar attendees are able to access this information by logging onto their Orielstat.com account.
How do we use your personal information?
We use information provided to orielstat.com to provide you with the information you requested; confirm and manage communications related to an order; respond to your comments, questions, and requests; and provide customer service and support.
We also use the information we collect about you to send you information related to your purchases, marketing information (including featured seminars and newsletters), and other news or information about Oriel STAT A MATRIX. You may opt out of receiving information that does not relate to a specific purchase or registration by visiting your profile and opting out of some or all correspondence.
Only with your prior consent, information pertaining to a training you participated in may be shared with the organization that certified the class (e.g., IRCA, Exemplar Global).
Information about our users may be employed to investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access to Oriel STAT A MATRIX services, and other illegal activities.
We also use personal information to understand user behavior and overall experience on our website.
How do we protect your data?
Oriel STAT A MATRIX does not sell, trade, or rent the personal information we collect. We will share your data only in the specific scenarios listed below.
For purchases paid for by credit card on our online store, your information is used to get approval from your credit card company.
For participants in training certified by third parties, we may request to share your information with the certifying body in order to satisfy requirements for attaining certification status for a particular class.
We may disclose your information to a third party if (a) we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; (b) to enforce our agreements, policies, and terms of service; (c) to protect the security or integrity of Oriel STAT A MATRIX services; (d) to protect Oriel STAT A MATRIX, our customers, or the public from harm or illegal activities; or (e) to respond to an emergency that we believe in good faith requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person. We may also share aggregated or anonymized information that does not directly identify you with third parties.
We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
How do I manage how much information I share or if I share any at all?
Visitors to orielstat.com residing within the EU are opted out of marketing communications by default
You can opt out of all marketing-related communications at any time. Every marketing-related communication includes an “unsubscribe” button to facilitate removal or preference updates. Please note, however, that you cannot opt out of communications related to registrations in our public seminars (e.g., course confirmations, invoices, course prework emails).
To update your Orielstat.com account information, log onto your account via orielstat.com and make any necessary changes; this will update your information pertaining to any public seminar registrations. You may also contact us directly at:
By email: privacy@orielstat.com
By post:
Oriel STAT A MATRIX
1095 Morris Avenue
Suite 103B
Union, NJ 07083
Attn: Privacy Control
By phone: 800.472.6477
Contact privacy@orielstat.com to request deletion or a copy of the data we’ve collected about you.
What is Oriel STAT A MATRIX doing to protect my privacy?
This site has security measures in place to protect it from the loss, misuse, and alteration of information under our control. Our servers use encrypted methods for the pages that contain personally identifiable data, including your credit card information and your address. We routinely monitor and upgrade our security systems to ensure that we use the best security technology available. Our hosting platform, Pier 1, complies with GDPR requirements.
Credit card transactions
Oriel STAT A MATRIX does not store your credit card information in our systems. All credit card transactions are processed using secure encryption – the same level of encryption used by leading banks. Card information is transmitted, stored, and processed securely at gateways on a PCI-compliant network.
In the case of a suspicious or declined transaction, our company may contact you to confirm the validity of the card and ensure your identity, or to cancel that transaction with full notification.
In the event that an order cannot be completed, please contact our Customer Service department (customerservice@orielstat.com). If our website cannot establish a secure connection, we will not risk your confidential information (i.e., the information will not be transmitted).
Conditions of use, notices, and revisions
If you choose to visit Orielstat.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this notice and our conditions of use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of New Jersey. If you have any concern about privacy at Orielstat.com, please send a thorough description to our Customer Service team (customerservice@orielstat.com) and we will try to resolve it.
Our business changes constantly. This notice and the conditions of use will also change, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the privacy notice in effect at the time of use. Please check our website frequently to see recent changes.
At Oriel STAT A MATRIX, we are sincerely committed to a safe and secure web experience for our visitors. If, after reading this, you have concerns or questions, please do not hesitate to contact us in one of the following ways:
Send an email to customerservice@orielstat.com
Send hard-copy mail to the following address:
Oriel STAT A MATRIX
1095 Morris Avenue
Suite 103B
Union, NJ 07083
Attn: Privacy Control
Cookie policy and usage
Oriel STAT A MATRIX automatically collects usage data through the use of cookies – small text files a website uses to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user’s ongoing access to the site, and facilitate the use of the site.
Different cookies do different things. Some are essential to the operation of a website, whereas others are not.
The information below describes the cookies we use on our site and why we use them. If you are located in the European Union, by clicking “Accept” you explicitly agreed to cookies being used while browsing the site. For detailed guidance explaining what cookies are and how to control or delete them, we recommend you visit http://www.youronlinechoices.eu.
The cookies we set
If you create an account with us, then we will use cookies for management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out; however, in some cases they may remain afterward to remember your site preferences when you’ve logged out. We use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are typically removed or cleared when you log out to ensure that you can only access restricted features and areas when logged in.
When you submit data to us through a form such as those found on contact pages or comment forms, cookies may be set to remember your user details for future correspondence. These are cookies that are set by this website directly and cannot be deactivated because they are required for the site to function. The web server uses nonpersistent cookies (not permanently saved on your computer) to save your choices while browsing the site. These are necessary cookies to support the basic functionality of the web experience (e.g., choice of language).
Google Analytics cookies
We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behavior. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here, and what you click on. This data is not tied to personally identifiable information. We do not collect or store your personal information (e.g., your name or address), so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.
This site uses Google Analytics, which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solutions on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit, so we can continue to produce engaging content.
As we sell products, it’s important for us to understand statistics about how many of the visitors to our site actually make a purchase, As such, this is the kind of data that these cookies will track. This is important to you, because it means that we can accurately make business predictions that allow us to monitor our advertising and product costs to ensure the best possible price.
You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy with regard to its analytics service at https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en.
Marketo cookies
This site uses an automation system provided by Marketo Inc., which employs cookies to recognize you as a unique user when you return to the site, and to track various data related to your website usage in order to provide custom content or services related to your specific interests.
The cookies placed by the Marketo server are readable only by Marketo. For more information on Marketo cookies and what they are used for, see the official Marketo site at http://www.marketo.com/trust/legal/privacy/.
Social media cookies
On our blog, you will see “social buttons.” These enable users to share or bookmark webpages or access Oriel STAT A MATRIX content on these social media sites. These buttons include Google+, Facebook “Like,” and LinkedIn “Share.” By clicking on any of these buttons, the site will register your action and may use that information.
To implement these buttons and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, scripts from domains outside of Oriel STAT A MATRIX must be used. You should be aware that when you are logged into the services of these sites (e.g., Google and Facebook), it is likely that they’re collecting information about your browsing habits, including when you’re on the Oriel STAT A MATRIX site, even if you do not click on a social button. Read the respective policies of each of these sites to see how they use your information and how to opt-out or delete such information.
Updates
We reserve the right change this cookie policy at any time. Any changes will become effective as soon as they are posted. Your continued use of our site constitutes your agreement to all such changes.
Disabling cookies
Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of this site. Therefore, it is recommended that you do not disable cookies. If you disagree with the use of cookies, you have the following options:
You can delete cookies after having visited the site.
You can browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” in Internet Explorer, and “Private Browsing” in Firefox and Safari).
You can set your browser’s security controls so that all or certain cookies are blocked.
You can request that we delete any personal information that we store – to do so, email privacy@orielstat.com.
Do not track
If you prefer not to use any cookies, you can also opt out in some browsers by turning on “Do Not Track” or visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices to opt out directly. We currently do not support Do Not Track browser settings, but are committed to supporting it in the future once there is a consistent industry standard for compliance.
How to contact us
If you have questions about this cookie policy, please contact us at: privacy@orielstat.com.
Get answers right now. Call 1.800.472.6477
< Back
